- [Maury] The Drama
happens right now on Maury.
It's an outrageous hour of DNA drama.
- My husband's not the
father of your baby.
- That's why I'm not your baby father!
- Why do you think he's denying her?
- Cause that google eyed (beep).
(shouting)
- No you can't, you can't deny this!
(cheering)
- I have two kids, light brown skin.
This baby is cocoa crisp.
- We're gonna find out right now.
Cory.
(cheering)
- I was 16 years old when
I found out I was pregnant.
- And then he said he wasn't the father.
- I can't be tied down to a baby
that don't even belong to me.
(audience jeering)
- What are you so upset about?
- Because I've never cheated on him!
- Eric.
- You are the father!
(cheering)
- [Maury] Two kids, denied by one man.
Today, Raymond is here with
his 'new fiance' Lakiesha.
- That's me, right here.
He is not the father.
- You've never met this woman have you?
- It's none of her business.
(audience jeering)
- Two kids.
- [Woman] Look at that,
they look just like him.
- [Maury] Is he the father
of one, two or none?
(cheering)
(dramatic music)
Shocking DNA results next.
- This is Tyisha everyone.
Now two years ago, Tyisha gave birth to a
beautiful baby girl named Sejadah.
(audience cooing)
Now almost immediately, this man Corey
began claiming he was not
(audience jeering)
(beeping)
Corey said he was not a hundred percent.
- No, no, no.
- He was two billion
percent sure that Sejadah
was not his daughter.
Now, to top it all off,
once Corey saw baby Sejadah,
he called her a horrible
name, that still bothers
Tyisha today, what was the name?
- Maury, the fool had the audacity
to call my child a bastard.
(audience shouting)
(beeping)
- Here's Tyisha's story.
- Corey is a sorry, pathetic,
no good excuse for a man.
And I'm here today to
prove that he is the father
of my daughter Sejadah.
I know this is all because
of his new wife Tawanna.
He was dating her before me so
I get that's why she jealous.
My baby look just like me and Corey,
she's a perfect mixture of the both of us.
Tawanna wasn't there in the bedroom,
so she don't know what
she's talking about.
She needs to get over the
fact that me and Corey
slept together, and stay out
of me and my child's life.
Corey and Tawanna, listen up,
when the results come back
that Corey is the father,
it's time to face the
truth, once and for all.
(cheering)
- But you see, Corey is
not here alone because
Corey has bought his wife Tawanna here.
(audience shouting)
- So what?
- Tawanna says, there
is no way her husband
is the father of Tyisha's baby.
- He's right, he bought him (beeps)
he brought his wife, that's right.
- He says two billion
percent he's not the father.
- Two billion percent man,
I don't even need a number
for how sure I am that
he's the father, come on.
He's the only man I was messing with.
(cheering)
- Now, are you surprised Tawanna's here?
- (beeps) No, (beeps) her
she never seen me before
and I never seen her, come on man,
why should she be in here.
- I seen a picture of you before
so I don't have to see you.
I seen your picture, you ugly bitch.
- Don't get mad cause
I look better than you
I'm at work today, stop playing.
- I don't care so what!
(shouting)
(audience screaming)
- You're just mad that
I look better than you,
I'm a worse threat, don't play with me.
- Whatever.
- That's right she (beeps).
- Right so has Corey
done anything for Sejadah
and the two of you?
- Hey aint done nothing
for her, not at all.
How you gonna sit up there,
you aint all that, come on man.
- So why do you think he's denying it?
- I truthfully he's
denying her because of that
google-eyed bitch right here!
- He didn't deny his child because of me!
He didn't deny his child because of me.
That aint his baby, so what?
It aint his baby.
It aint his baby, like
I say, it aint his baby.
- [Maury] You know what
he told my producers?
He said the condom got stuck.
(audience shouting)
- Condom got stuck?
- That's right, that's right!
I'm not your baby's father,
I'm not your baby father!
- The condom got stuck?
The condom got stuck?
Hang on, wait a minute, wait a minute.
- Stay out our life.
- [Maury] Alright now wait a minute.
Why are you so emotional?
- 'Cause any time, Maury,
any time you got the
audacity to call any child a bastard
it don't matter if it's his or not,
you don't call nobody's child a bastard?
(cheering)
You don't (beeps) it!
You don't talk about kids,
they didn't ask to be there!
- Okay okay okay, I got
it, I got it, guess what?
This is what Corey and Tawanna
have to say, watch this.
- I am here today, because I
am two billion percent sure
that I am not the father of Tyisha's baby.
I met Tyisha on a phone chat line.
I called Tyisha, for a one night stand,
and now I got a crazy bitch trying to say
that I'm the father of her child?
(record scratch)
To make matters worse,
she's trying to involve
my wife Tawanna.
She's just trying to
break up our marriage.
- Tyisha, my husband is not
the father of your baby.
Sejadah looks nothing like my husband,
she doesn't even look like Tyisha
no telling where the
hell that baby came from!
Tyisha, imma make this short, sweet,
and straight to the point.
I am not your baby daddy, so
leave me and my wife alone
and good luck with your search.
(audience jeering)
- Here they are, Corey and
Tawanna, here they are.
(shouting)
- Yeah, woo!
- Yeah, yeah, yeah!
(speech drowned out by shouting)
- We in love man, we love.
- Look at this, I mean look at this.
Look at this chocolate crisp baby here.
- So what if she look nothing like you?
- Yes, yes, yes!
(shouting)
- What does that expression
mean, you just called that baby?
What does that mean?
- (beeps) Maury, let me
break it down to you Maury.
- [Maury] Please.
- I have two kids, they
have light brown skin,
this baby is cocoa crisp.
She is a dark baby.
Maury let me break this down to you,
you arguing bitch, yep.
(shouting)
(cheering)
Hey Maury, Maury Maury Maury.
Maury.
- [Maury] Tyisha be quiet.
- Listen, listen, listen Maury.
Before y'all jump on her side,
she knows that I'm a good father.
I don't blame her, that she
want a good father in her life.
- Why don't you take in my daughter?
- So don't jump on her side yet.
Let's get the DNA results right now.
She crazy.
- Right.
We're gonna find out right now.
(cheering)
- [Tawanna] She crazy, she crazy!
She crazy!
- Now that I know if you're
the father you'd take care
of this child the way you
take care of your own.
- That's right, just like I
take care of my other children.
- He'd take care of her like
he take care of his others.
- Right okay, right.
When it comes to two
year old Sejadah, Corey,
you are the father!
(screaming)
(shouting)
- [Tyisha] I deserve an apology.
- I apologized to ya,
I'm gonna be a big man
and I'm apologizing.
- I deserve an apology from you too.
- Why?
- Hold on a second, wait a second.
Let him apologize, okay?
- I apologize to you, I was wrong, okay?
I'm gonna take care of this child,
just like I take care of my other child.
- That's it.
- I apologize to you.
(cheering)
- Very good.
Very good!
- I was 16 years old when
I found out I was pregnant.
- [Maury] And then he
said he wasn't the father?
- I can't be tied down to a baby
that don't even belong to me.
(audience jeering)
- What are you so upset about?
- I've ever cheated on him!
You are the father!
(cheering)
- [Maury] Two kids, denied by one man.
- Two kids!
- [Woman] Look at them
they look just like him!
- [Maury] Is he the father
of one, two or none?
(shouting)
The results are unforgettable,
and the results are in.
- 17 year old Magan once
dreamed of going to college
to become a pediatrician.
Today she has dropped out of high school,
is a single mother,
struggling to raise her
four month old son Brayden.
(audience cooing)
All of Magan's heartache is because
this 18 year old, Eric, refuses
to acknowledge paternity.
This is her story.
(beeping)
- I was 16 years old when
I found out I was pregnant.
I was lonely, I was scared,
I didn't know what to do.
I missed out on a lot of stuff
that I really wanted to do.
I'm sorry.
(sniffing)
I wanted to finish high
school, go to college
and be a pediatrician.
I never thought I would be a teen mom.
In the beginning, Eric was there for me,
through my pregnancy and
it meant so much to me.
- [Maury] Sadly, Eric's
support did not last.
- When I was seven months pregnant,
Eric started denying my son Brayden.
And now he calls my baby
ugly, retard, stupid.
- [Maury] Through this painful ordeal,
Magan's mother Jeanne,
has been by her side.
- The minute Magan told
me she was pregnant,
it broke my heart.
Then I knew that I was
gonna have to be the one
to take care of her and Brayden.
I have done everything for
Brayden that Eric has not.
- I'm only 17 and I can't do it by myself.
- Okay, we're gonna talk
to Magan's mother Jeanne
in a moment, but first, you
actually married the guy?
- Yeah.
(shouting)
- [Maury] When you were pregnant?
Brayden then called your baby names?
- Yeah, ugly, retarded, stupid.
(shocked shouting)
- How dare you call my
grandson stupid or retarded?
You have no right!
- But if he's calling Brayden
ugly, he's ugly his self.
(cheering)
- Before we hear from your mother Jeanne,
listen to what Eric had to say.
- I'm only 18 years old,
and I'm not even ready
to be a father yet, I have
my whole life ahead of me.
I can't be tied down to a baby
that don't even belong to me.
I know Magan was cheating
on me, I'd wake up in the
middle of the night and
I'd hear her talking
to these other guys on the phone.
Magan wouldn't even let me
see Brayden when he was born
why would I even think he's mine then?
Magan is a bitch, cause
all she does is lie.
She lied about cheating
on me, and she lied about
Brayden being my son.
I can't stand Magan's mother,
she needs to stay out of my life,
this is none of her business.
I just graduated high
school, I have my own goals,
and I'm not gonna let
Magan pin her baby on me.
(shouting)
- There he is, Eric, Eric come on out.
Here's Eric, you stay there.
(audience jeering)
Come on, sit down.
(beeps)
Eric, you ever seen this baby?
- No she wouldn't let me see him.
- You (beeps) liar!
You're a (beeps) liar Eric!
You little (beeps) liar!
- What are you so upset about Magan?
(shouting drowns out speech)
- And that baby looks
just (beeps) like him!
He looks just like him,
I never cheated on him!
He cheated on me Maury, he cheated on me!
(beeping)
- You said you're 18, you're
too young to be a father?
- You shouldn't have been
with me if you weren't
big enough to take on the responsibility?
(beeping)
(shouting)
- Eric, you say you're 18 and you're
too young to be a father right?
- I'm 17 Eric and I'm a (beep) mother!
You can't stand up and be a dad?
You can't do it Eric?
- Shut up.
- No (beep)
- There's never been a
moment to teach that Eric
if he'd ever been in that baby's life!
What kind of person are you?
Nobody stopped (beep) from seeing him!
You made that choice!
(beeping)
Idiot!
You need to grow up and (beep) boy!
And support your child and your wife!
(cheering)
- Why would you call somebody,
first of all, a baby,
why would you call a baby terrible names,
when you've never seen
the baby in your life?
- Because Eric's retarded, that's why!
- [Eric] I never called him names.
- Eric's stupid he has no common sense!
- I said he was a mistake.
(gasps)
- [Maury] Oh a mistake?
- That's it!
Why should I take care of a
baby that's not even mine?
- Eric, what are you gonna do?
- What happens if it is yours?
If it is yours, you gonna take care of it?
- Yeah I'll take responsibility,
and take care of the baby.
- [Maury] You will?
- Yeah I will.
- [Maury] Okay you will.
- We'll see about that,
you gonna get a job?
- I promise that, yeah.
- This is what Jeanne had to say, watch.
(beep)
- Eric how dare you use the excuse that
you're a teenager why you
can't take care of Brayden?
Whether you like it or
not, you made this baby
with Magan, and you gonna
take care of this baby.
Eric you're a worthless excuse for a man.
If the world was flat
I would push your ass
right off of it.
I makes me sick to my stomach
that you deny my grand baby.
- Here's Jeanne, Jeanne come on out.
(cheering)
(beeps)
What are you up in his face about?
- He's a liar.
- [Maury] He's a what?
- It's all he ever does is lie.
- I'm not a (beep) liar!
- Yeah you are, that's
all you know how to do!
- Well it's none of your business anyway!
- It is totally my business,
this is my daughter
and I'm supporting them right here.
(cheering)
What part of that do
you not understand Eric?
- You're just a stupid
(beep), that's all you are.
- Well you know what Eric,
you don't need to be talking your mouth,
your smack, your bumping your
gums a little bit too much.
Maybe you need to learn a
lesson, you need to grow up boy!
(cheering)
You, you are the one who
wanted to get her pregnant!
- Why don't you shut (beep).
- [Maury] Eric, you think
that baby looks like you?
(shouting)
- I supported you for a year,
so don't tell me (beep) my business!
- That's (beep).
How you gonna prove it?
Prove it (beep).
(shouting)
- [Maury] Jeanne, (beep) up.
- Can I have those when
you're done reading them?
- I buy the wipes, I buy his
clothes, I bought his bed
I bought everything that that baby has!
(cheering)
You aint paid for nothing!
So what kind of a man are you?
You aint a man.
- [Maury] Alright Jeanne
isn't this more (beeps).
- [Jeanne] Yes.
- When it come's to four
month old Brayden, Eric,
- You are the father!
I'll say it for you.
- [Maury] You are the father!
(cheering)
(beeping)
Just take care of that child okay?
- Yeah I will.
- Alright, that's all I know.
- [Maury] Two kids denied by one man.
Today, Raymond is here with
his 'new fiance' Lakiesha.
- That's me, right here,
he is not the father!
- [Maury] You've never
met this woman have you?
- It's none of her business.
(audience jeering)
- Two kids.
- [Woman] Look at them
they look just like him!
- [Maury] Is he the father
of one, two or none?
(shouting)
The results are unforgettable,
and the results are in.
This is Shanae.
Shanae is furious, with this
man Raymond, for denying
that he fathered not one,
but two of her children.
(shouting)
Three year old Raymond junior and
one and a half year old Phoenix.
Now what makes Shanae really furious
is that here's the deal with Shanae.
This is why she believes that
Raymond is acting this way.
She says he acts this way
every time Raymond gets a new girlfriend,
he denies his kids.
So today Raymond is here with
his 'new fiance' Lakiesha.
- That's me.
Right here, that's me!
He is not the father!
- They're determined to prove
that Shanae is wrong, watch.
- Shanae, you know as well as I know
that these kids are not mine.
- What kind of woman has
Raymond waiting 15 hours
for your kids, and you don't even show,
that makes you a nasty,
manipulative bitch.
- [Raymond] How dare you
give Raymond junior my name.
He's not even my blood.
And you tricked me into
signing that birth certificate
just so you can get child support off me.
- Raymond junior has red hair,
he's not even as dark as my man.
Don't you dare say that
this is none of my business.
Any whore that takes advantage of my man,
becomes my business.
- And as for Phoenix,
we weren't even together
when you got pregnant.
So how do I know she's mine?
- [Lakiesha] You are nothing but a lying
childish, poor excuse for a mother.
Quit calling, and leave my man alone.
- [Maury] How about that?
What do you think of that?
- (beeps) That's none
of her (beep) business.
It's none of her business.
These are my kids, these
are me and Raymond's kids,
this is none of her business.
- That's my business!
(shouting)
- No it's not, that's my business!
- [Lakiesha] My man!
- No, it's none of her
business like I said,
it's none of her business, it's between me
and her so-called man.
- Yes it is, it's my
business, he's my (beep) man!
- By the way, how long do you
think she'll stick around?
- Mm, six months.
(shouting)
- Already been there three years!
Three years already.
- It's her, this aint even her business
I didn't lay down with
her and make these babies.
- [Lakiesha] It's my business,
it's definitely my business.
- Two kids.
- [Shanae] Two kids.
- Both kids he's got?
- I have two beautiful kids.
(cheering)
Two beautiful kids.
- Well let me ask you, do you
think those kids look alike?
- Look at my daughter!
Look at my son!
Look at them, they look just like him.
They look just like him.
Look at my babies.
- Not his kids, you're
a liar, kiss my (beep).
These (beep) are yours!
- Nothing but lies.
- So, okay, Raymond
junior's like three right?
- [Shanae] He's three.
- He's three, what has Raymond
done for Raymond junior?
- He bought my son a can
of milk, and six outfits.
Everybody in this world
know it takes more than
a can of milk and six outfits.
In three years, in three years.
He has done nothing.
- [Maury] And what about Phoenix?
Who's a year and a half?
- Nothing he's done absolutely nothing.
- [Maury] Okay you've never
met this woman have you?
This is the first time you ever saw her.
- First time I see her ugly ass.
- We're gonna bring
her out here right now,
here they are, Raymond
and his fiance Lakiesha.
(audience jeering)
Now you sit over here.
I didn't even ask this question.
In the beginning, did
you deny these babies?
- I denied them.
- [Shanae] No he did not.
No he did not, you were
at the hospital side,
I have pictures of you holding my son,
you didn't deny it
Raymond and you know it.
Matter of fact, you
asked my mom and my dad
can you marry me?
Don't sit up here and lie.
(cheering)
Do not sit up here and lie.
- [Raymond] Where are they
at, where are they at?
It's your word over mine, that's it.
- Exactly, and when that test come.
- [Maury] Raymond you know what she says?
Every time you get a new
woman this is how you act.
- Ask her how many womans
have I had since her?
- Womans, womans?
Women you mean?
Women you mean, women you mean?
Shut your old ass up.
- No (beeps)
- This is none of your business.
You are too old to be with him.
- How do you know?
- You need to get a real man and
quit being with a little boy.
- I look better than you!
- You are 40 years old!
(shouting)
Keep out of my business.
- You came into my business.
- I don't have anything
else to say to you,
I'm better than you.
I am better than you.
(shouting)
(beeps)
Get your woman and sit down.
- Why aren't you the
father of that little girl?
- Cause I wasn't around.
- [Maury] You weren't around?
- I was not around.
- She cheated!
- We were together in Las
Vegas, we were living together
in Las Vegas when I got
pregnant with my daughter.
- [Maury] Raymond, if you're the father
are you gonna take care of these kids?
- If I get to see 'em, that's only it.
If I don't get to see
'em, she can keep 'em.
- He hasn't done it.
- Would you let him get
involved in these kids lives?
- If he needed to, yeah.
Excuse me, let me rephrase that.
If he was man enough to
come around without her.
(cheering)
- When it comes to one and
a half year old Phoenix,
Raymond, you are the father.
(cheering)
- Can I get an apology?
Okay.
(beeps)
- When it comes to three
year old Raymond junior,
Raymond, you are not the father.
(shouting)
(beeps)
- See, she cheats!
She (beeps) cheats!
(shouting)
- We'll ask to help you find the
father of Raymond junior alright?
We can help you.
He's the father of that little girl, okay?
He's the father of that little girl.
- I can't believe this.
- [Maury] What do you mean,
you couldn't believe he was
the father of either one of them?
- I can't believe he's the father
of any one of them is right.
- [Maury] We'll he's the father of one.
Shenae swears that no one
else could be the father,
and you won't believe the reason why.
- My little Gabriel was
born with birth defects,
and the doctor said that if he didn't
have the surgery, that he would die.
- He says you were cheating.
- Your free ride is over.
- I never cheated on you.
He needed you and you
weren't there for him.
- [Maury] Did he father this baby?
Michael.
The results are unforgettable,
and the results are in.
This is Anna, now when Anna met Michael,
she thought they were a
perfect match, made in heaven.
Now, two weeks after the
baby Gabriel was born,
two things.
(audience cooing)
Two things happened,
that shocked Anna to the core.
First, the doctors discovered that
Gabriel had birth defects.
(audience sighs sadly)
And would need life threatening surgery.
Secondly, Michael then
accuses Anna of cheating,
and told her, he didn't think
he was the sick baby's father.
This is Anna's story.
- I am furious at Michael,
when we met in college
two years ago he pretended
to be mister right.
Me and Michael were living together,
we were planning on getting
married and having this baby.
But the whole time, he was
accusing me of cheating on him.
What really broke my heart
is what happened the day
that Gabriel was born.
He said that he didn't even
think he was the father.
My little Gabriel was
born with birth defects
and the doctor said that if
he didn't have the surgery
then he would die.
How could Michael deny a
baby that needs him so much?
Today I'm gonna prove that
Michael is the father,
so he can step up and be
a dad to our miracle baby.
- Okay, alright so Anna first
of all, Gabriel came through
that surgery, he's great,
there's no problem, right?
- He's doing fine.
He's perfect.
(cheering)
- [Maury] Why are you
so angry at that man?
- Because Maury, I am sick
and tired of his (beep)
I am tired of him not
being there for his son,
I am tired of him promising
to come and see the baby.
I have kept the baby up late past bed time
waiting for him to come see him.
- [Maury] Oh he promises to come?
- He promises to come see him,
he shows up at one o'clock in the morning,
what nine month old is gonna be awake at
one o'clock in the morning?
I even let my baby go and
stay at a family member of his
house so he could spend
the night with his father,
he didn't even come home!
My baby was there for two days,
and he never come home to see him.
He stayed at a different
family members house.
- Because he says you were cheating.
- I never cheated on him, never in my life
did I ever cheat on him.
(cheering)
- [Maury] You're positive he's the father?
- I am a million percent
sure he is the father.
- [Maury] So I mean
when did all this start?
You were together, you were a couple?
- We were together, he
even asked me to marry him.
- [Maury] So why would he think
that you were cheating on him?
- Because he had friends
and family members
trying to convince him that
I was and all I wanted to do
was trap him with this baby.
- Oh is that what it was?
I see.
Did he know about the birth defects?
- Yes he was there when the
doctor told us about it.
He knew about the birth
defect, he knew about the
neurosurgeon appointment, he did not go
to the first two doctors
appointments with me.
- Before we bring him
out, this is what what
Michael had to say.
- Anna is a liar.
She had sex with her
friends, and my friends
behind my back.
She was with another guy the night
the baby was conceived.
I have been there for
this baby even though
I don't think he is mine.
Anna wants me back, but
that's not gonna happen.
Anna, I know you're after my money.
When I've proved that I am not the father,
pack up your bags, pack up the baby
cause you're out of my house.
Your free ride is over.
- Wait a minute.
(audience jeering)
- [Anna] Free ride, oh my god!
There is no free ride.
- Wait a minute, wait a
minute, wait a minute.
- [Anna] What money?
- [Maury] Are you all living together?
- We were.
- [Maury] Where do you live right now?
- I live in his house, he
packed up and went to one of his
family members because he got mad.
- [Maury] Do you want him back?
- Honestly, yeah I would like
to work things out with him
because our baby needs both
of us, he needs his father
as well as me.
- Here's Michael, Michael come on out.
(audience jeering)
- I cheated on you?
How can you say he's
not yours, look at him!
I never cheated on you.
Look at that baby, look at that baby!
Look at your baby, that is your baby!
- That's bull!
- He needed you and you
weren't there for him!
When have you ever been there for him?
His family has been there
for him more than you have.
- I have been there
for him the whole time.
- Where were you his
first doctors appointment?
Where are you at when he
screams, "daddy, daddy, daddy"?
Where?
No where.
- Michael, she says your
family members or friends
are convincing you of this.
- Well I walked into her
apartment and she was
laying on top of another guy.
(audience shouting)
- And where were you?
Where were you?
- [Maury] Well, if you
are the father you'd be
in that child's life right?
- Oh yes, that's why she's
at my house right now.
- [Maury] Oh the baby's at your house?
- Yeah and he aint there, he's not there.
- Yeah the baby's with my grandmother.
- I see, now let me ask you this
if you are the father are you
all gonna get back together?
- We'll have to work on it.
- [Maury] Oh really?
- [Anna] We'll have to
have a lie detector.
- We will have to work on it.
- [Maury] It's a possibility?
- It is a strong possibility.
- Oh good well let's find out then.
(cheering)
When it comes to nine month old Gabriel,
Michael, you are the father!
- See, I told you, I told you!
Look at him!
- Alright, alright.
- I told you, I told you.
- That's why I've been there.
- Well you know what?
You need to be there more now.
- You can not work things out
when you get into his face.
- I told you, I told you.
- I buy diapers, I come and
get him and hang out with him.
- [Maury] You've proved
your point alright.
You say that you wanna get back together,
he may wanna get back together,
so let's build an atmosphere
that can bring that about, okay?
- (sniffs) I told you.
- Boy, you all look at each
other like there's no way
you're gonna get back together.
- He's a got a lot of
making up to do. (beep)
- I have been there.
- Guess what you have to do?
You have to have a big
enough heart to accept him.
(cheering)
- I love you.
- I love you too.
- [Maury] Her son is
denied for one reason.
Ernest's sister, Jeanetta.
(shouting)
- She wasn't there when I slept
with him, she was not there.
(audience jeering)
- [Maury] The results are unforgettable,
and the results are in.
This is Jessica.
Jessica is heartbroken
that her ex-bofriend Ernest
continues to deny her eight
month old son Ernest junior.
(audience cooing)
- [Ernest] That aint me, that's not me.
- Jessica says, the number
one reason responsible
for this emotional drama is
Ernest's sister, Jeanetta.
(audience jeering)
- No way, no way.
- You see it was Jeanetta, the
sister who called the show.
And Jessica blames her
for putting so much doubt
in Ernest's heart.
Listen to what Ernest and
Jeanetta have to say, watch this.
- Jessica, I'm a trillion
percent sure that my brother
is not your son's father.
- Jessica when I let you move in with me,
I know you were sleeping
with one of my friends,
and I know one of them
might be the father.
Back in the days, I didn't
think of how dirty you was,
cause I was in love with you.
But when I found out you had four kids,
with four different fathers,
I knew you was a hoe.
- I'm gonna protect my
brother from a nasty,
trifling bitch like you.
- You would stay out until
five o'clock in the morning
and I know you was creeping
cause that's what hoes do.
- Today is the day we find the truth,
and when we do you better back off.
- I want you to change his name,
leave my family the hell alone and go find
your real baby father.
(shouting)
- [Maury] What do you think of that?
- She wasn't there when I slept with him,
she was not there!
I'm a hundred percent sure
that he's (beep) the father!
Hey, where the (beep) picture at?
Where is the (beep) at?
Where is the picture at?
Here, tell me, do they look alike?
Please tell me, oh, what!
What!
- Jessica.
- Yes.
- They look alike.
- Yeah he looks just like his son does!
- No.
- You nasty, you know you nasty too!
- [Maury] So you and Ernest were
going together is that right?
- Yes, we was together for like two years
I known him for eight years,
that's why I been sat here, (beeps).
- [Maury] Jeanetta was
the one who made the call.
- Yes, I don't know why, she
was not sleeping with us.
She was away in New York
while me and him was in VA.
You need to get a reality check bitch.
(cheering)
- You're a bitch.
You hoe, you a skanky hoe.
- Jessica.
- Me and his sister was close!
- You're lying.
They gonna apologize
when this paternity test.
Yeah you're lying, be
a man, be a (beep) man.
(cheering)
- He is a man.
- You a hoe, you a hoe.
- Did Ernest say to you he would
always be there for you and your son?
- Yes he said that he would
never leave me and my son,
he loved us forever.
- We're gonna bring
them out here, alright?
Ernest and Jeanetta.
(beeps)
Here they are.
(audience jeering)
- Whatever, you guys don't know nothing!
You don't know nothing!
- Hi Maury.
- Ernest, Ernest, Ernest!
- [Ernest] Yes.
- Look.
Look at those pictures.
- That baby don't look
like me first of all.
You see that mole on his head?
None of these people in my
family got no mole on their head.
(shouting)
This like somebody who was
in the crib, at my crib.
Get out of here, he aint my son.
Whatever man, you a hoe man.
- That's your baby, why you dressing up,
you need to back up-
- You a hoe.
- Ernest, Ernest, did you say you (beep)
Did you say that you would
be there for that child
because you've seen all these guys
who never wanted to pony up
to take care of these kids?
- Well that was until I found out
what type of girl she was.
- [Maury] Really.
- No, no, no, no!
- It's because he didn't
know that she has four kids
by four different men.
- Did you or did you not say
that you would not want a baby by me?
- [Maury] Jeanetta,
Jeanetta, wait a second.
- [Jeanetta] Yes Maury?
- You aint tell me about it.
- What is that Maury?
- [Maury] Jeanetta, why
are you in this Jeanetta?
- Because this is my little brother
and I'm gonna back him up,
from any little hoe like that.
(shouting)
- You all don't know nothing, man.
Get out of here.
- My brother, my brother, my brother!
- That aint my baby get out of here.
- Oh sit down.
(shouting)
- I'm gonna be super soaking my arms.
Super soak bitch, hey!
- We're gonna find out right now.
- Sit your ass down.
- [Jeanetta] Give us those results Maury.
- Jeanetta, is this baby is your brothers,
I want you back in the life of that baby.
- I want y'all to go apologize to him
and kiss him on his feet.
(cheering)
- When it comes to eight month old,
by the way, if this is your child,
you'll take care of this child?
- Yes, I will.
- [Maury] He's got your name.
- When it comes to eight
month old Earnest junior,
Earnest-
Is his sister right or wrong?
Shenae swears that no one
else could be the father,
and you won't believe the reason why.
The results are unforgettable,
and the results are in.
(dramatic music)
- [Maury] So you and
Ernest were going together.
- Yes, we was together for like two years,
I know him for eight years (beeps)
- And did Ernest say to you
he would always be there
for you and your son?
- Yeah he said that he would
never leave me and my son,
he loved us forever.
- Jessica when I let you move in with me,
I know you were sleeping
with one of my friends,
and I know one of them
might be the father.
Back in the days, I didn't
think of how dirty you was
cause I was in love with
you, but when I found out
you had four kids with
four different fathers
I knew you was a hoe.
- [Maury] Why are you in this Jeanetta?
- Because this my little
brother and I'm gonna
back him up from any little hoe like that.
(shouting)
- When it comes to eight
month old Earnest junior
Earnest, you are the father!
(shouting)
- That's crazy, that's crazy man.
Oh my god man, I don't believe this man.
- [Maury] You'll be a good aunt.
- She'll be a (beep).
(cheering)
- I'm sorry I accused
you of stuff that you
didn't do, I guess I'm sorry.
- Jessica, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I am, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- I miss you.
- [Jeanetta] Hi bo, hi jo-jo!
- I love you.
- [Jeanetta] Hi jo-jo!
Hi jo-jo.
- [Maury] Shanae swears that
no one else could be the father
and you won't believe the reason why.
The results are unforgettable,
and the results are in.
(dramatic music)
Earlier, Shanae came to our
show to prove to Raymond
and his new fiance Lakiesha,
that he was the father
of her two kids.
Two kids?
- [Shanae] Look at them they
look just like like him.
- [Maury] The paternity test proved
Raymond fathered her daughter.
But the second DNA test sent
shock waves through our studio.
- [Maury] You are not the father.
(cheering)
Backstage, executive
producer Paul Faulhaber
spoke with an emotional Shanae.
- He's the only guy I slept with.
I don't even sleep with guys.
- [producer] What do you mean?
I'm a lesbian, he's the
only guy I slept with.
- [Producer] Well that's impossible,
I saw the test myself, it's
okay, listen, you're a good mom.
- [Maury] We hope that
when Shanae gets home
she can find the answers
she's looking for.
Until next time America.
(dramatic electronic music)
(rattling)
(birds tweeting)
(orchestral music)